YWCA of the U.S.A. Records. Record Group 8. Community Associations
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES IV. COMMUNITY ASSOCIATIONS FILES
  - Subseries B. 1988-2002
    - Ohio
      - Medina County
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1998 (Box 941)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 941)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1979,1996 (Box 941)
        - Correspondence, 1988-2000, n.d. (Box 941)
        - Program, 1997-98, n.d. (Box 941)
      - Piqua
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 942)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 942)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 942)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 942)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1995 (Box 942)
        - Correspondence, 1991-99, n.d. (Box 942)
        - Program, 1992-98, n.d. (Box 942)
      - Salem
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 942)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 942)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1996-97 (Box 942)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 942)
        - Board of Directors, 1992-99 (Box 942)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1996 (Box 942)
        - Correspondence, 1990-99, n.d. (Box 942)
        - Program, 1976-98, n.d. (Box 942)
      - Steubenville
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 942)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1994-98 (Box 942)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1996-97 (Box 942)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 942)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1914, 1996 (Box 942)
        - Correspondence, 1988-2001, n.d. (Box 942)
        - Program, 1990-2000, n.d. (Box 942)
      - Summit County/Akron Area/Akron
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 942)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-98 (Box 942)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1996, 1998 (Box 942)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 942)
        - Board of Directors, 1991-98 (Box 942)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1986-97 (Box 942)
        - Correspondence, 1986-2001, n.d. (Box 942)
        - Program, 1994-98, n.d. (Box 942)
      - Toledo
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 942)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 942)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 942)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 942)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1996 (Box 942)
        - Correspondence, 1990-98, n.d. (Box 942)
        - Program, 1993 (Box 942)
      - Van Wert County (Van Wert)
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 942)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1994-99 (Box 942)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995 (Box 942)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 942)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1996 (Box 942)
        - Correspondence, 1990-2001 (Box 942)
        - Program, 1998, n.d. (Box 942)
      - Warren
        - Accreditation requirements
          - 1991-94 (Box 942)
          - 1995-99 (Box 943)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 943)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1996-97 (Box 943)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 943)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1996 (Box 943)
        - Correspondence, 1990-2001, n.d. (Box 943)
      - Williams County/Bryan
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-97 (Box 943)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-97 (Box 943)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995 (Box 943)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 943)
        - Board of Directors, 1990-94 (Box 943)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1984-98 (Box 943)
        - Correspondence, 1986-2001, n.d. (Box 943)
      - Youngstown
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-97 (Box 943)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-97 (Box 943)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1998 (Box 943)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 943)
        - Board of Directors, 1990-98, n.d. (Box 943)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1994, 1996 (Box 943)
        - Correspondence, 1988-2000, n.d. (Box 943)
        - Program, 1987-97, n.d. (Box 943)
      - Zanesville
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 943)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1995-97 (Box 943)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 943)
        - Board of Directors, 1991-97 (Box 943)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1998 (Box 943)
        - Correspondence, 1990-2000, n.d. (Box 943)
        - Program, 1988 (Box 943)
    - Oklahoma
      - Ardmore
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 943)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 943)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1998 (Box 943)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 943)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1996, 1999 (Box 943)
        - Correspondence, 1987-2001, n.d. (Box 943)
        - Program, 2000 (Box 943)
      - Bartlesville
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-98 (Box 943)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1987-98 (Box 943)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995 (Box 943)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 943)
        - Board of Directors, 1988-97 (Box 943)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1994, 1998 (Box 943)
        - Correspondence, 1987-2001, n.d. (Box 943)
        - Program, 1949-97, n.d. (Box 943)
      - Enid
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 943)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1987-99 (Box 943)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 943)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 943)
        - Board of Directors, 1987, 1999 (Box 943)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1995, 1999 (Box 943)
        - Correspondence, 1987-2001, n.d. (Box 943)
        - Program, 1981-99, n.d. (Box 943)
      - Oklahoma City
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 944)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 944)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1994-95 (Box 944)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 944)
        - Board of Directors
          - General, 1988-2000 (Box 944)
          - Strategic planning materials, 1994 (Box 944)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1963, 1993-95 (Box 944)
        - Correspondence, 1988-2001, n.d. (Box 944)
        - McFarland Branch, 1995-96 (Box 944)
        - Program, 1993-2000, n.d. (Box 944)
      - Tulsa
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-98 (Box 944)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1989-97 (Box 944)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1993, 1996-97 (Box 944)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 944)
        - Board of Directors, 1987-99, n.d. (Box 944)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1975, 1997 (Box 944)
        - Correspondence, 1979-2001, n.d. (Box 944)
        - Program, 1984-99, n.d. (Box 944)
    - Oregon
      - Portland, Greater/Portland
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 944)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1992-99 (Box 944)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1993, 1996-97 (Box 944)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 944)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1944, 1985-96 (Box 944)
        - Correspondence, 1988-2000 (Box 944)
        - Program, 1994-2001 (Box 944)
      - Salem
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-98 (Box 945)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-98 (Box 945)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1994-97 (Box 945)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 945)
        - Board of Directors, 1990-98 (Box 945)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1914-96 (Box 945)
        - Correspondence, 1988-2001, n.d. (Box 945)
        - Program, 1991-98, n.d. (Box 945)
    - Pennsylvania
      - Allentown
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 945)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1993-98 (Box 945)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995-98 (Box 945)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 945)
        - Board of Directors, 1992-98 (Box 945)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1953-97 (Box 945)
        - Correspondence, 1980-2001, n.d. (Box 945)
        - Program, 1989-98, n.d. (Box 945)
        - Racial Justice Task Force, 1991 (Box 945)
      - Altoona
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 945)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 945)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 945)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 945)
        - Board of Directors, 1992-97 (Box 945)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1935-96 (Box 945)
        - Correspondence, 1990-99 (Box 945)
        - Program, 1973, 1992-98, n.d. (Box 945)
      - Bethlehem
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 945)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 945)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1996-97 (Box 945)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 945)
        - Board of Directors, 1992-96 (Box 945)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1930, 1986-96, n.d. (Box 945)
        - Correspondence, 1985-99 (Box 945)
        - Program, 1991-2001 (Box 945)
      - Bradford
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-97 (Box 945)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-97 (Box 945)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 945)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 945)
        - Board of Directors
          - 1988-91, 1996 (Box 945)
          - 1997-2001 (Box 946)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1984, 1998, n.d. (Box 946)
        - Correspondence, 1989-2001 (Box 946)
        - Program, 1991-98, n.d. (Box 946)
      - Bucks County
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-97 (Box 946)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-97 (Box 946)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1996-97 (Box 946)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 946)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1955-96 (Box 946)
        - Correspondence, 1990-2001, n.d. (Box 946)
        - Program, 1992-2001, n.d. (Box 946)
      - Butler
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 946)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 946)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1998 (Box 946)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 946)
        - Board of Directors, 1994-99 (Box 946)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1976-95 (Box 946)
        - Correspondence, 1989-99 (Box 946)
        - Program, 1990-91, n.d. (Box 946)
      - Carlisle
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 946)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 946)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 946)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 946)
        - Board of Directors, 1995-2001 (Box 946)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1919-95 (Box 946)
        - Correspondence, 1988-98 (Box 946)
        - Program, 1973-97 (Box 946)
      - Chester
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-98 (Box 946)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1995-98 (Box 946)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1997 (Box 946)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 946)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1995 (Box 946)
        - Correspondence, 1991-2002 (Box 946)
        - Program, 1994-99, n.d. (Box 946)
      - Chester County/Greater West Chester/West Chester (see also Coatesville)
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 947)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 947)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1996-97 (Box 947)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 947)
        - Board of Directors, 1987-95 (Box 947)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1964-96 (Box 947)
        - Correspondence, 1991-2001, n.d. (Box 947)
        - Program, 1992-2000 (Box 947)
      - Coatesville (see also Chester County)
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-95 (Box 947)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1977 (Box 947)
        - Correspondence, 1989-99 (Box 947)
        - Program, 1993-94 (Box 947)
      - Easton
        - General, 1990-94 (Box 947)
        - Personnel confidential, 1991 (Box 947)
      - Erie
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 947)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 947)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1998 (Box 947)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 947)
        - Board of Directors, 1996-98 (Box 947)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1984, 1998 (Box 947)
        - Correspondence, 1989-95 (Box 947)
        - Program, 1995-99 (Box 947)
      - Germantown
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-95 (Box 947)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991 (Box 947)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1998 (Box 947)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1980, 1999 (Box 947)
        - Correspondence, 1988-2001 (Box 947)
        - Program, 1991-2000, n.d. (Box 947)
      - Gettysburg and Adams County/Gettysburg
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-97 (Box 947)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 947)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1993, 1995, 1998 (Box 947)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 947)
        - Board of Directors, 1995-99 (Box 947)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1978, 1995 (Box 947)
        - Correspondence, 1992-2000 (Box 947)
        - Program, 1997-98 (Box 947)
      - Hanover
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-98 (Box 947)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-98 (Box 947)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 947)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 947)
        - Board of Directors, 1995-96 (Box 947)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1924-95 (Box 947)
        - Correspondence, 1988-99, n.d. (Box 947)
        - Program, 1992-97, n.d. (Box 947)
      - Harrisburg, Greater
        - Accreditation requirements
          - 1991-93 (Box 947)
          - 1994-99 (Box 948)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 948)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1993, 1995, 1997 (Box 948)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 948)
        - Board of Directors, 1995-96 (Box 948)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1982, 1996 (Box 948)
        - Correspondence, 1988-2000 (Box 948)
        - Program, 1992-98, n.d. (Box 948)
      - Hazleton
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 948)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 948)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1993, 1995, 1997 (Box 948)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 948)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1914-96 (Box 948)
        - Correspondence, 1988-99 (Box 948)
        - Program, 1997-98 (Box 948)
      - Johnstown, Greater
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 948)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1994-99 (Box 948)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1993, 1995, 1997 (Box 948)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 948)
        - Board of Directors, 1994 (Box 948)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1995 (Box 948)
        - Correspondence, 1989-2001 (Box 948)
        - Program, 1995, n.d. (Box 948)
      - Lancaster
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 948)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-98 (Box 948)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 948)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 948)
        - Board of Directors, 1995-97 (Box 948)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1996 (Box 948)
        - Correspondence, 1993-99 (Box 948)
        - Program, 1991-2001 (Box 948)
      - McKeesport
        - Accreditation requirements, 1995-99 (Box 948)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 948)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 948)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 948)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1996 (Box 948)
        - Correspondence, 1992-99 (Box 948)
        - Program, 1993-94, n.d. (Box 948)
      - Meadville
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-98 (Box 948)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-98 (Box 948)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1997 (Box 948)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 948)
        - Board of Directors, 1996 (Box 948)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1914-2000 (Box 948)
        - Correspondence, 1989-99 (Box 948)
        - Program, 1988, 1995-97, n.d. (Box 948)
      - Montgomery County, Central (Norristown)
        - Accreditation requirements, 1993-95 (Box 948)
        - Correspondence, 1989-98, n.d. (Box 948)
      - Oil City
        - Accreditation requirements
          - 1990-93 (Box 948)
          - 1994-99 (Box 949)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-98 (Box 949)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 949)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 949)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1993, 1995 (Box 949)
        - Correspondence, 1996-99 (Box 949)
      - Philadelphia
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-98 (Box 949)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1997-98 (Box 949)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 949)
        - Application for Community YWCA Status, 2001 (Box 949)
        - Board of Directors, 1991-98 (Box 949)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1870-1998 (Box 949)
        - Correspondence, 1982-99, n.d. (Box 949)
        - Program, 1991-98, n.d. (Box 949)
      - Pittsburgh, Greater
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 949)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 949)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1993, 1995, 1997 (Box 949)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 949)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1892, 1990-96 (Box 949)
        - Correspondence, 1990-99 (Box 949)
        - Program, 1990-98, n.d. (Box 949)
      - Pottstown
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-97 (Box 949)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-97 (Box 949)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 949)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 949)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1974-95 (Box 949)
        - Correspondence, 1995-99 (Box 949)
      - Pottsville
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 950)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-97 (Box 950)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1998 (Box 950)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 950)
        - Board of Directors, 1998 (Box 950)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1929, 1933, 1996 (Box 950)
        - Correspondence, 1991-2002 (Box 950)
        - Program, 1997, n.d. (Box 950)
      - Shamokin
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-97 (Box 950)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-97 (Box 950)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1993, 1997 (Box 950)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1997 (Box 950)
        - Correspondence, 1990-2001, n.d. (Box 950)
      - Titusville
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 950)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 950)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1996, 1998 (Box 950)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 950)
        - Board of Directors, 1991, 1998 (Box 950)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1998 (Box 950)
        - Correspondence, 1990-2002 (Box 950)
        - Program, 1991-98, n.d. (Box 950)
      - Warren
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-97 (Box 950)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-97 (Box 950)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1993, 1995 (Box 950)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1995 (Box 950)
        - Correspondence, 1989-98 (Box 950)
      - Washington County
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-97 (Box 950)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-97 (Box 950)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1993, 1995 (Box 950)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1993 (Box 950)
        - Correspondence, 1989-2000 (Box 950)
        - Program, 1995-97, n.d. (Box 950)
      - Westmoreland County/Greensburg
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 950)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 950)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1993, 1995, 1997 (Box 950)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 950)
        - Board of Directors, 1994-99 (Box 950)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1996 (Box 950)
        - Correspondence, 1991-99 (Box 950)
        - Program, 1991-97, n.d. (Box 950)
      - Williamsport
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 950)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1994-2000 (Box 950)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1998 (Box 950)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 950)
        - Board of Directors, 1997-2000 (Box 950)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1898 (Box 950)
        - Correspondence, 1988-2000 (Box 950)
        - Program, 1992-98, n.d. (Box 950)
      - York
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 950)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 951)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1998 (Box 951)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 951)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1996 (Box 951)
        - Correspondence, 1991-2000 (Box 951)
    - Rhode Island
      - Greater Rhode Island
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 951)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 951)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1993, 1995 (Box 951)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 951)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1996 (Box 951)
        - Correspondence, 1982-2002 (Box 951)
      - Northern Rhode Island (Woonsocket)
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 951)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-2000 (Box 951)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 951)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 951)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1998 (Box 951)
        - Correspondence, 1996-2000 (Box 951)
        - Program, 1998-99 (Box 951)
    - South Carolina
      - Aiken: Initial Community Information, 1993 (Box 951)
      - Charleston, Greater
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-98 (Box 951)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-98 (Box 951)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1996 (Box 951)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 951)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1970-96 (Box 951)
        - Correspondence, 1989-99 (Box 951)
        - Legal: trademark infringement, 1968-75 (Box 951)
        - Program, 1971-98, n.d. (Box 951)
      - Greenville
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-98 (Box 951)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-98 (Box 951)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 951)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 951)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1994-95 (Box 951)
        - Correspondence, 1990-2001 (Box 951)
        - Program, 1991-96, n.d. (Box 951)
      - The Midlands/Columbia
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 951)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1992-99 (Box 951)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1998 (Box 951)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 951)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1987, 1996 (Box 951)
        - Correspondence, 1988-99, n.d. (Box 951)
        - Program, 1992-98 (Box 951)
      - Upper Lowlands/Sumter Area
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 951)